A DI DE or 9A B OD AN VL 71 ON 9E.
♫‫أ دي دي دي O R 9A B‬♫ ‫OD AN VL 71 ON‬ ‫تسعة‬
BAMORO 9ABOBOANVL7ION9E
BAMOR9ABOANVION9E
Here you are.
‫أنت هنا‬
You're here. You're here.
ليو كاي آن أنت هنا بالفعل
Hello, Mr. Chen.
‫مرحباً سيد تشين‬
Miss Kiki, I'll keep my dignity.
‫الآنسة Kiki سأحافظ على السلوك‬
Don't intervene in others' lives.
‫لا تتدخل في حياة الآخرين‬
Do less evil things.
لا تفعل أشياء سيئة.
Chen Yalu.
تشين يا لو
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
Look at this.
انظر ما هذا
Junteng Capital.
شركة جيون تنغ للاستثمار
Only the higher-ups have a gold card.
البطاقة الذهبية فقط من المستوى الأعلى
Let me introduce myself.
دعني أقدم نفسي
I'm the senior investment manager of Junteng Capital.
أنا مدير الاستثمار العالي لشركة جيون تنغ
Kiki.
‫كيكي‬
I've been interested in Kaixi Entertainment for a long time.
‫لقد أحببت وكاشي للترفيه منذ وقت طويل‬
I went for an interview
‫ذهبت للمقابلة‬
to test
من أجل التحقق
Unfortunately, I didn't win your favor.
لكن من المؤسف أنني لم أرك
But I'm glad.
لكن أنا سعيد جدا
At least you are very strict in handling people.
على الأقل أنتم صارمون جدًا في خدمة الناس
It's so lively today.
‫اليوم مفعم بالحيوية‬
Kiki.
‫كيكي‬
Is this Mr. Liu and Mr. Chen
هل هذا الشخص
Mr. Liu and Mr. Chen?
الرئيس ليو والسيد تشين
Hmm.
نعم
This is the senior investor consultant of Junteng Capital,
هذا مستشار المستثمر العالي لشركة جونتنغ للاستثمار
and deputy general manager, Mr. Ji Jiang.
نائب المدير العام السيد جي جيانغ
Hello, President Ji.
مرحبا أيها المدير جي
Mr. Chen, do you still think
أيها المدير تشن هل ما زلت تعتقد
with good intentions?
نيتك الحسنة
Miss Kiki, I'm really sorry.
‫الآنسة كيكي أنا آسفة حقاً‬
I was too impulsive just now.
‫لقد كنت متهوراً جداً للتو‬
I apologize.
أعتذر لك
I'm not that...
أنا لست
"Ma" means interests.
ما المصالح الأول
I won't give up
المشاريع التي أحبها
I won't give up even if I'm being chased.
لن أستسلم حتى لو طاردني أحد
President Ji, Miss Kiki.
المدير جي آنسة كيكي
So you really want to vote for Kaixi?
إذًا، هل ستصوت لـ كاي شي حقًا؟
Mr. Liu, to be honest,
‫سيد ليو، بصراحة
If it weren't for Kiki's recommendation,
إذا لم يكن Kiki يرشح هذا
I don't know much about your company.
‫أنا حقاً لا أعرف أي شيء عن شركتك‬
Here's the thing.
الأمر هكذا
President Ji, Miss Kiki.
المدير جي آنسة كيكي
Today, let me introduce Kaixi.
اليوم سأعرفكم على كاشي
our project.
المشروع التالي
Mr. Liu, today is the weekend.
سيد ليو اليوم هو عطلة نهاية الأسبوع
Let's not talk about work.
لا نتحدث عن العمل
Can we have a drink here?
هل يمكننا الجلوس هنا لشرب كأس
Sure. Please.
نعم نعم تفضل
President Ji, Miss Kiki, please support us.
المدير جي الآنسة Kiki تشجعي
Here.
هيا
Yale, don't you want a title?
"يا لو"، ألا تريد مكانتك؟
I'll give you all the shares and houses.
سأعطيك كل الأسهم والمنزل
I told you
لقد أخبرتك
I, Liu Kaian,
أنا ليو كاي آن
a petty person.
ليس شخص بخيل
It's just a matter of time.
فقط مشكلة الوقت
Kaian, I'm sorry.
كاآن أنا آسف
I was too sensitive.
أنا حساس جدا
When are they coming to the office?
متى سيأتون إلى الشركة
Tomorrow.
غدًا، لكن آمل أن يأتوا للحديث الآن.
Yale, you should come tomorrow and dress up.
‫يا لو، تعالي غداً وترتدي ملابس جيدة‬
I'll definitely beat Kiki.
‫يجب أن تقارن Kiكي‬
I haven't seen you so happy for a long time.
‫لم أراك سعيدة هكذا منذ وقت طويل‬
We don't hold a wedding.
نحن لا نقيم حفل الزفاف
It's just a gathering of relatives and friends.
فقط اجتماع الأقارب والأصدقاء
and let everyone see their new wife.
فقط اجعلنا نرى الزوجة الجديدة
Chun Xiang, I have something to say.
تشون شيانغ
What are you doing?
ما الذي تفعله
I haven't found my daughter-in-law yet.
لم أجد زوجة الابن بعد
Another one.
مرة أخرى
I'm going to poke you.
‫هذا يجعل الناس يضربون عمودك
I'm not going. That's it.
لن أذهب، هذا كل شيء
Hey.
آه آه آه
Mr. Ji, you can invest in it first.
أيها المدير جي، هل حقاً يمكننا استثمار أولًا؟
Don't worry, Mr. Liu.
اطمئن سيد ليو
This is our initial cooperation.
هذا هو تعاوننا الأولي
I always follow the rules.
أنا دائما أهتم بالقواعد
I’ll get some money soon.
سأحصل على بعض المال خلال هذه الفترة
Thank you, Mr. Ji.
شكرا لك المدير جي
You're welcome.
لا داعي للشكر
You should thank Kiki.
‫إذا أردت أن تشكريها فلتشكري Kiki‬
I've never seen her
‫هذه أول مرة أراها‬
such a person.
معجبة بشخص كهذا
I do value
أنا حقا أهتم
Kaixi's potential and ability.
قدرة كاشي ومهارة المدير ليو
I really admire Miss Kiki.
‫أنا معجب جداً بالآنسة كيكي‬
She knows more about Kaixi than me.
‫إنها تعرف كاشي أكثر مني‬
Of course. Otherwise,
بالطبع وإلا
become a senior investment manager?
‫كيف تصبحين مديرة الاستثمار العالي‬
President Ji, Miss Kiki,
المدير جي آنسة كيكي
I've prepared a feast.
لقد أعددت مأدبة عائلية
Please do me the honor.
من فضلك
Mr. Liu, here's the thing.
‫سيد ليو، الأمر هكذا
We have a rule.
لدينا قوانين
we can't get too close to our partners.
لا يمكن الاقتراب من الشريك
However,
‫لكن‬
Kiki can go.
‫يمكن Kiكي الذهاب‬
Then I'll do as you say.
‫إذن فأنا مطيع‬
Have some tea.
اشرب الشاي
Thank you.
شكرا
I'm so full
لقد شبعت جداً
Your cooking is amazing.
مهارة طبخ خالتي رائعة حقًا
No, it's just some home-cooked dishes.
لا  كل هذه الأطباق المنزلية
My name is Kaian, a big hotel.
طلبت من كاآن أن حجز فندق كبير
He insisted on having a family dinner.
أصر على إقامة مأدبة عائلية
It's the best treat.
إنه أفضل ضيف
I don't know.
‫لا أفهم‬
Anyway, I'm happy that you can eat well.
‫على أي حال أنا سعيد جداً أن تأكل الآنسة كيكي جيداً‬
Just call me Kiki from now on.
‫يمكنك مناداتي Ki في المستقبل‬
You too.
‫أنتم أيضاً‬
Don't be so polite. Just call me by my real name.
لا تكن غريبًا، نادوني باسمي الحقيقي
Okay, you can call us by our name too.
حسنًا يمكنك أن تنادينا أيضًا
Since we're friends, don't be so distant.
بما أننا أصدقاء، لا تكن غرباءً
Be closer.
أقرب
Yes, it's better to be closer.
نعم نعم
I'll cut some fruits.
تحدثا، سأقطع بعض الفاكهة
Okay.
حسنا
Thank you.
شكرا يا خالتي
Kaian, when I came to your house,
كاآن جئت إلى منزلك
I know why you are so excellent.
عرفت لماذا أنت ممتاز
Mom loves you.
أمك تحبك
My wife loves me and my son.
زوجتي تحبها ولديها
You told me that men's ideals
قلت لي حلم الرجال من قبل
That's all.
مثل هذا
I'm satisfied anyway.
على أي حال أنا راضية جدا
He even talked about men's dreams with you.
هل تحدث معك عن حلم الرجال
He never talked to me.
لم يتحدث معي قط
You husband and wife only talk about private things.
أنتما زوجان تتحدثان فقط عن بعض الكلمات السرية
We outsiders can't listen.
لا يمكننا أن نسمع الغرباء
By the way,
بالمناسبة
I heard you have a daughter.
سمعت أن لديك ابنة
Why didn't you see her?
لماذا لم أرها
She's at her grandma's.
إنها في منزل جدتها
Oh.
أوه
I'm full too.
لقد شبعت أيضا
I want to get up and exercise.
أريد أن أقف لأتحرك
Yalu.
يا لو
Why don't you show me around your house?
ما رأيك أن ترافقني لزيارة منزلك؟
Sure.
حسنا
Actor table.
‫جدول الممثلين‬
[Ni Ying Yang as Liu Kaian]
‫ني ليان يانغ تمثل ليو كاي آن‬
Playing Xu Jinxi
‫تشو فو أر تمثيل شو شي‬
Kei as Yan Jiaying
‫يان جيا ينغ تمثل كيكي‬
X Wang as Chen Yalu
‫وانغ شينغ تشن زي تشين يا لو‬
Zheng Tuo jiang as Ji Jiang
تشينج تاوجيانغ
Anyu as Wu Chun Xiang
[وو تشون شيانغ]
Cao Lihua as Xu Mu
تساو لي هوا
Zhang Jianing as Yi Yi.
[تشانغ جيا نينغ]
Liu Weizhou as Lu Wenjun
ليو وي تشو
to perform.
‫المشاركة في العرض‬
Hello. Hello.
تشو يا
Libin Liu.
ليو لي بين
Wei Chuan.
وي تشوان
He Chang Wang Jing Wang Yu
‫خه تشانغ وانغ جينغ وانغ يوي‬
Zhang Yaxiu.
[تشانغ يا شو]
Chae-yun.
[لو ساي يون]
Zhao Xueyun.
تشاو شين
Han Chao.
هان تشاو
Zhao Yi Cheng.
تشاو يي تشنغ
Xu Zhenbin.
شو تشن بين
Chen Man-gu.
تشين وان تشيو
[Staff Table]
[جدول الموظفين]
Director team.
‫فريق المخرج‬
Director Liu Gang Yu Ge.
المخرج ليو قانغ يو جي
Photography team.
مجموعة التصوير
Lighting Team.
مجموعة الأضواء
The recording team.
مجموعة التسجيل
Art team.
مجموعة الفن
The styling team.
مجموعة التصميم
The production team.
‫فريق المنتج‬
The venue team.
فريق الشؤون
Hello. Hello.
فريق السائق
Late production.
‫الإنتاج في المرحلة المتأخرة
Tianjin Jiayi Culture Co., Ltd.
‫شركة جيا يي الثقافية في مدينة تيانجين‬
["The Disappearing Love"]
["حبيب مفقود"]
[Written by Jang Ji-hwan]
["جانغ جي هوان"]
Production Company.
[شركة الإنتاج]
Tientsin Film Pictures Co., Ltd.
شركة محدودة للسينما المحدودة في تيانجين
Product Company.
شركة المنتجات
[Tianjin Film Co., Ltd.]
شركة المنتجات المشتركة
Beijing Gaxi Culture Co., Ltd.
شركة محدودة للإعلام الثقافية بكين
Beijing Wonderful Forest Movie and Culture Co., Ltd.
شركة محدودة الثقافة الغابة الرائعة في بكين
Beijing Deep Technology Co., Ltd.
شركة تقنية عميقة في بكين
Ming Xie Group.
أشكر شركتنا
Tientsin Yu Castle International Hotel.
‫فندق تيانجين يو جيا باو الدولية
Tientsin Hilton Hotel.
"فندق "هاردون" في "تيانجين"
Beijing Handan Steel Hotel.
فندق الميلاد في بكين